<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Society for Open Software</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Society for Open Software</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2022 [Sarthak Shah](https://untyped.ml) &amp; [SOS Members](https://github.com/orgs/BITS-SOS/people). [CC-BY-SA](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 23:45:32 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cruxipher</title>
      <link>/posts/cruxipher/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 22:48:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/cruxipher/</guid>
      <description>For ATMOS 2022, we worked with Crux on Cruxipher - a CTF event that tested software development, cryptography and UNIX skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shell Basics</title>
      <link>/posts/shell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 22:47:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/shell/</guid>
      <description>The Shell Basics workshop was conducted on the first of October. The workshop covered the basics of using shell interfaces such as bash and zsh.
Poster for the workshop:
(Made in GIMP, as usual) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dualbooting Workshop</title>
      <link>/posts/dualboot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 21:27:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dualboot/</guid>
      <description>Our very first event as a society was a workshop on dualbooting Linux with Windows.
It took place on 19th June, 2022 at F204 in the OAB.
Here is a clip from the event: This was the poster for the event: (Made in GIMP, of course) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members</title>
      <link>/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 20:49:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/members/</guid>
      <description>Sarthak Shah - President Site: untyped.ml Github Soumitra Shewale - Secretary Site Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apply</title>
      <link>/apply/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 20:49:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/apply/</guid>
      <description>We require all members to run some GNU/Linux distro on their laptops in single or multi-boot. Some experience with using the command-line shell is expected, but not strictly necessary.
If you feel like you satisfy these requirements, you can apply by filling this form. Upon receiving the form, we will send you an e-mail with interview details.
Please note that there might be slight delays in interview timings if there are ongoing exams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 20:36:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>BITS-SOS is an independent society established in BITS Pilani, Hyderabad Campus with the aim of increasing awareness about free and open source software and raising the rate of GNU/Linux adoption on campus. We regularly hold events and workshops related to GNU/Linux and open source technologies such as Bash and Git.
Our members are listed here along with their details. To join us, click ./apply.
You can find out more about free software here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
